Register of the Marshall Green papers
Hoover Institution Archives
Marshall Green papers
1898-1998
1960-1998
98066
Hoover Institution Archives
31 manuscript boxes (12.4 linear feet)
The Marshall Green papers consist of speeches and writings, correspondence, dispatches, memoranda, reports, studies, and printed matter relating to American foreign policy in East Asia, especially with regard to China, Korea, and Japan; American foreign relations with Indonesia and Australia; the Vietnam War; and international population problems and American governmental population policy. They originate from Green's official assignments with the State Department, extensive professional travels, and role in discussions of global population issues. Digital copies of select records also available at https://digitalcollections.hoover.org.
Green, Marshall
Access
Collection is open for research. Digital copies of select records also available at https://digitalcollections.hoover.org.
As required by law, folders of security-classified materials have been removed from the collection until they can be declassified by government officials. Upon declassification, the materials are available in the Declassified U.S. Government Records series listed at the end of the collection.
The Hoover Institution Archives only allows access to copies of audiovisual items. To listen to sound recordings or to view videos or films during your visit, please contact the Archives at least two working days before your arrival. We will then advise you of the accessibility of the material you wish to see or hear. Please note that not all audiovisual material is immediately accessible.
Acquisition Information
Acquired by the Hoover Institution Archives in 2002.
Accruals
Materials may have been added to the collection since this finding aid was prepared. To determine if this has occurred, find the collection in Stanford University's online catalog at http://searchworks.stanford.edu/. Materials have been added to the collection if the number of boxes listed in the online catalog is larger than the number of boxes listed in this finding aid.
Alternate Forms Available
Digital copies of select records also available at https://digitalcollections.hoover.org.
Biographical Note
1916 January 27 Born, Holyoke, Massachusetts
1939 A.B., Yale University
1939-1941 Private Secretary to American Ambassador to Japan
1942 February 14 Married Lispenard Seabury Crocker
1945 Vice Consul, Career Secretary, Diplomatic Service
1946-1947 Assigned, Wellington, New Zealand
1947-1950 Acting Officer in charge of Japanese affairs, Department of State
1950-1955 First Secretary, Embassy Consulate, Stockholm, Sweden
1955-1956 Assigned, National War College, Washington, D.C.
1956-1959 Regional Planning Advisor for Far East, Department of State
1959-1960 Acting Deputy Assistant Secretary of State
1960-1961 Minister Counselor, American Embassy, Korea
1961-1963 American Consul General, Hong Kong (personal rank of minister)
1963-1965 Deputy Assistant Secretary for Far Eastern Affairs, Department of State
1965-1969 Ambassador to Indonesia
1969 Member, U.S. team in Paris for Vietnam negotiations Recipient, National Civil Service Award
1969-1973 Assistant Secretary of State for East Asian-Pacific Affairs, Washington, D.C.
1973-1975 Ambassador to Australia and Nauru
1975 Chairman, Task Force on Population, National Security Council
1975-1979 Coordinator, Population Affairs, Department of State
Scope and Content of Collection
The Marshall Green papers consist of speeches and writings, correspondence, dispatches, memoranda, reports, studies, and printed matter relating to American foreign policy in East Asia, especially with regard to China, Korea, and Japan; American foreign relations with Indonesia and Australia; the Vietnam War; and international population problems and American governmental population policy. They originate from Green's official assignments with the State Department, extensive professional travels, and role in discussions of global population issues.
Letters between Henry Kissinger and Green in the Correspondence series shed light on President Richard Nixon's trip to Asia, resumption of talks with China, and the Vietnam settlement. However, the bulk of the materials in this collection can be found in the Office File. They relate to countries and regions in which Green served--their history and the impact of their government policies on the United States. This series also includes materials relating to President Nixon's trip to China and his communications with Green about Asia between 1969 and 1972. Green's speeches in Australia, as well as his speeches relating to population affairs, especially immigration and refugee issues, are also included in this series.
Green's travel reports, submitted primarily to the State Department, though one on China was directed to President Nixon, are included in the Travel File. They record his general observations on the political, economic, and social scene in Asia and Africa, its effects on population growth, and the status of family planning programs.
Arrangement
Organized into nine series: Biographical File, Correspondence, Speeches and Writings, Office File, Travel File, Subject File, Computer Disk, Photographs, and Declassified U.S. Government Records.
United States. Department of State.; Australia--Foreign relations--United States.; Diplomats--United States.; East Asia--Foreign relations--United States.; Indonesia--Foreign relations--United States.; Population.; United States--Foreign relations--Australia.; United States--Foreign relations--East Asia.; United States--Foreign relations--Indonesia.; Vietnam War, 1961-1975.
- Biographical File, 1921-1998
  Scope and Contents note
  Clippings and printed matter, "humor" file, letters of commendation and thanks, naval service file, and records of awards and honors, arranged alphabetically by physical form.
  - Clippings and printed matter, 1975-1995 (Box-folder 1: 1)
  - "Humor" file
    Includes charts, clippings and printed matter, correspondence, poems, and speeches and writings.
    - General, 1921-1998 (Box-folder 1: 2-3)
    - "Mission control file,", 1984 (Box-folder 1: 4)
  - Letters of commendation and thanks
    Includes memoranda.
    - ABC TV, "Issues and Answers,", 1972 (Box-folder 1: 5)
    - Air War College, 1965 (Box-folder 1: 6)
    - The Alan Guttmacher Institute, 1984 (Box-folder 1: 7)
    - Aylward, Robert A., 1963 (Box-folder 1: 8)
    - Battle, Lucius D., 1964 (Box-folder 1: 9)
    - Drake University, 1964 (Box-folder 1: 10)
    - Gillem, Alvan C., II, 1971 (Box-folder 1: 11)
    - Hitchcock, David I., 1997 (Box-folder 1: 12)
    - Hodges, Luther H., 1964-1965 (Box-folder 1: 13)
    - Hogan, Michael, 1963 (Box-folder 1: 14)
    - Jones, G. Lewis, 1965 (Box-folder 1: 15)
    - Kim Chung-Yul, 1963 (Box-folder 1: 16)
    - Manning, Robert J., 1964 (Box-folder 1: 17)
    - Morrow, John H., 1964 (Box-folder 1: 18)
    - Pierce, Bob, 1963 (Box-folder 1: 19)
    - Porter, Dwight J., 1964 (Box-folder 1: 20)
    - Rostow, W. W., 1974 (Box-folder 1: 21)
    - Rubottom, R. Richard, Jr., 1963-1964 (Box-folder 1: 22)
    - Stingle, Howard E., 1964 (Box-folder 1: 23)
    - Tchah Kyun Hi, 1964 (Box-folder 1: 24)
    - Underhill, Frank T., Jr., 1963 (Box-folder 1: 25)
    - Yale University, 1973-1992 (Box-folder 1: 26)
    - Young Presidents' Organization, Inc., 1964 (Box-folder 1: 27)
  - Naval service file, 1953-1955 (Box-folder 1: 28)
    Assignment to Ready or Standby Reserve, 1953 January 1, and letter of resignation and honorable discharge, 1955 October 24.
  - Records of awards and honors
    - Rockefeller Public Service Award nomination in the field of Foreign Affairs and International Operation, 1961, 1973, 1980, and 1981 (Box-folder 1: 29)
    - Distinguished Honor Award, Department of State, 1979 (Box-folder 1: 30)
    - Director General's Cup Award, Foreign Service, Department of State, 1981 (Box-folder 1: 31)
    - 40-Year Service Award, Foreign Service, Department of State, 1983 (Box-folder 1: 32)
    - Second Class Order of Rising Sun, 1985 (Box-folder 1: 33)
    - Organizing Committee, Harry S. Truman Awards for Outstanding Contributions to International Cooperation and to Improving Conditions of Life, 1991-1996? (Box-folder 1: 34)
      Includes related materials and drafts on Purposes and Challenges of the Program prepared by Marshall Green.
  - Miscellany, 1995 (Box-folder 1: 35)
- Correspondence, 1940-1997
  Arranged alphabetically by name of correspondent. Includes some letters neither to nor from Green.
  - Unidentified, 1975-1997 (Box-folder 2: 1)
  - Abt Associates, Inc., 1993 (Box-folder 2: 2)
  - American Association for the Advancement of Science, 1988 (Box-folder 2: 3)
  - Barnett, Robert W., 1975 (Box-folder 2: 4)
  - Breer, William T., undated (Box-folder 2: 5)
  - Center for International Policy, 1984 (Box-folder 2: 6)
  - Colantonio, Ernest J., 1974 (Box-folder 2: 7)
  - Davidson College, 1987 (Box-folder 2: 8)
  - Daytona-Beach Sunday News Journal, 1965 (Box-folder 2: 9)
  - Groton School, 1973-1975 (Box-folder 2: 10)
  - Hall, Walter Vance, 1965 (Box-folder 2: 11)
  - Hubbard, Charlotte M., 1964 (Box-folder 2: 12)
  - Jonathan Edwards College, 1940 (Box-folder 2: 13)
  - Journal of International Law and Politics, New York University, 1988 (Box-folder 2: 14)
  - Kennedy, Charles Stuart, 1995 (Box-folder 2: 15)
  - Kissinger, Henry, 1969-1971 (Box-folder 2: 16)
    Includes collected material about Kissinger. See also: Box 6, Folder 5.
  - Lavin, Bernard J., 1982 (Box-folder 2: 17)
  - Mahran, Maher, 1990 (Box-folder 2: 18)
  - Smith, Ralph, 1997 (Box-folder 2: 19)
  - Tatu, Frank, 1986 (Box-folder 2: 20)
  - Taylor, Samuel, 1980 (Box-folder 2: 21)
  - Turner Broadcasting System, Inc., 1984 (Box-folder 2: 22)
  - Warner, John J., Mrs., undated (Box-folder 2: 23)
- Speeches and Writings, 1948-1998
  Articles, conference papers, drafts of writings, letters to the editor, notes, statements, and testimony, arranged chronologically. Additional speeches are included in the Office File.
  - General
    - General, 1981-1991 (Box-folder 2: 24)
    - Drafts of writings - unidentified
      - Undated (Box-folder 2: 25-26)
      - 1960-1985 (Box-folder 2: 27)
      - 1986-1990 (Box-folder 3: 1)
      - 1991-1995 (Box-folder 3: 2)
      - 1996-1998 (Box-folder 3: 3)
    - Fragments, undated (Box-folder 3: 4)
    - Letters to the editor, 1979-1995 (Box-folder 3: 5)
    - Notes
      - Notebooks and diary notes, 1954-1974 (Box-folder 3: 6)
      - Speech notes
        - Undated (Box-folder 3: 7)
        - 1970-1989 (Box-folder 3: 8)
  - Untitled, undated (Box-folder 4: 1)
  - "Adversary Role in U.S. Foreign Policymaking," article, undated (Box-folder 4: 2)
    Typescript.
  - Comments to be made on political subjects, undated (Box-folder 4: 3)
    Typescript and holograph notes.
  - "Diplomatic Memoirs: The Serious and Lighter Moments by an Old Far East Hand,", undated (Box-folder 4: 4)
  - Interview, Larry Keegan, undated (Box-folder 4: 5)
    Typescript transcript and holograph notes.
  - "New Perspectives in U.S.-East Asian Relations," article, undated (Box-folder 4: 6)
  - Statement, Subcommittee on Asian and Pacific Affairs, Committee on Foreign Affairs, United States House of Representatives, undated (Box-folder 4: 7)
  - Testimony, Committee on Foreign Affairs, United States House of Representatives, undated (Box-folder 4: 8)
  - "The U.S.-China-Japan Triangle in Long-Term Perspective," speech, undated (Box-folder 4: 9)
  - Interview, future relations between China, Japan, and the U.S., Takahama, Special Representative, Yomiuri Shimbum, 1948 March 25 (Box-folder 4: 10)
    Printed copy.
  - "John Foster Dulles and the Taiwan Straits Crisis,", 1958
    General note
    See also: Box 7, Folder 28.
    - Background materials (Box-folder 4: 11)
    - Holograph (Box-folder 4: 12)
    - Typescript (Box-folder 4: 13)
  - "Communist China: A Problem in U.S. Policymaking," article, 1965 May (Box-folder 4: 14)
  - Remarks, meeting of U.S. delegates to Paris talks on Vietnam, 1969 February 13 (Box-folder 4: 15)
  - "Modesty, Mutuality and Multilateralism in Foreign Affairs," concluding remarks on Indonesia, American Club of Paris, 1969 March 5 (Box-folder 4: 16)
  - Statement, Subcommittee on Foreign Operations, Committee on Appropriations, United States House of Representatives, 1969 July 14 (Box-folder 4: 17)
  - "A New Approach in East Asia,", 1969 August 28
    - Correspondence (Box-folder 4: 18)
    - Holograph (Box-folder 4: 19)
    - Typescript (Box-folder 4: 20)
  - Statement, Subcommittee on Foreign Operations, Committee on Appropriations, United States Senate, 1969 November 26 (Box-folder 4: 21)
  - "U.S. Policy toward a Changing Southeast Asia," address, American University, Washington, D.C., 1970 January 28 (Box-folder 4: 22)
  - Statement, Subcommittee on Foreign Operations, Committee on Appropriations, United States House of Representatives, 1970 April 15 (Box-folder 4: 23)
  - "A Strategic Appraisal of the Pacific Area," speech, Seventeenth Annual National Security Forum, Air War College, Alabama, 1970 May 11-17 (Box-folder 5: 1)
  - "Test of the Seventies," concluding remarks, Chiefs of Missions Conference, Tokyo, 1970 July 9-11 (Box-folder 5: 2)
    Typescript. Includes related material.
  - "U.S. Policy toward Red China: A Review," statement, Subcommittee on Asian and Pacific Affairs, Committee on Foreign Affairs, United States House of Representatives, 1970 October 6 (Box-folder 5: 3)
    Typescript and printed copy.
  - Statement, Committee on Foreign Affairs, United States House of Representatives, 1970 November 30 (Box-folder 5: 4)
  - "The Nixon Doctrine: A Blue Print for the 1970's," newsletter, United States Department of State, 1971 January (Box-folder 5: 5)
  - "The Nixon Doctrine: A Progress Report," address, Far East American Council, Plaza Hotel, New York City, 1971 January 19 (Box-folder 5: 6)
  - Address, U.S. policy in East Asia, 1971 March 29 (Box-folder 5: 7)
  - Statement, Committee on Foreign Affairs, United States House of Representatives, 1971 May 4 (Box-folder 5: 8)
  - "United States Policy toward the People's Republic of China," address, U.S.-China National Committee, 1971 June 4 (Box-folder 5: 9)
  - Statement, Subcommittee on Operations, Committee on Appropriations, United States House of Representatives, 1971 June 14 (Box-folder 5: 10)
  - "The Drug Problem in East Asia," statement, Subcommittee on Asian and Pacific Affairs, Committee on Foreign Affairs, United States House of Representatives, 1971 July 9 (Box-folder 5: 11)
  - "End-of-the-War Hearing," statement, Subcommittee on Asian and Pacific Affairs, Committee on Foreign Affairs, United States House of Representatives, 1971 July 12 (Box-folder 5: 12)
  - Statement, acceptance of an invitation to join Congressman Benjamin S. Rosenthal on a trip to New York, 1971 July 23 (Box-folder 5: 13)
  - "The Challenge of Constructive Cooperation," keynote address, 1971 Conference on Asia, Far East America Council, Plaza Hotel, New York City, 1971 October 4 (Box-folder 5: 14)
  - Address, Executive Committee, U.S.-Japan Governors Conference, St. Louis, Missouri, 1971 October 27 (Box-folder 5: 15)
  - Statement, Subcommittee on Foreign Economic Policy, Committee on Foreign Affairs, United States House of Representatives, 1971 November 3 (Box-folder 5: 16)
  - Statement, Committee on Foreign Affairs, United States House of Representatives, 1972 March 23 (Box-folder 5: 17)
  - Interview, "Meet the Press," Lawrence E. Spivak, 1972 March 26 (Box-folder 5: 18)
    Typescript and printed copy. Includes related material.
  - Remarks, Air Force Academy, Colorado Springs, Colorado, 1972 April 12 (Box-folder 5: 19)
  - "Breakthrough," New York Times, 1972 April 15 (Box-folder 5: 20)
  - Statement, Subcommittee on Operations, Committee on Appropriations, United States House of Representatives, 1972 April 18 (Box-folder 5: 21)
  - Statement, Subcommittee on Asian and Pacific Affairs, Committee on Foreign Affairs, United States House of Representatives, 1972 May 2 (Box-folder 5: 22)
  - Remarks, Ditchley Conference, 1972 May 18-22 (Box-folder 5: 23)
    Holograph notes.
  - "Multipolar Asia and Southeast Asian Neutralization," speech, East Asia Chiefs of Mission Conference, Hong Kong, 1972 June 23-25 (Box-folder 5: 24)
    Typescript. Includes a letter from K. K. Tse.
  - Remarks, Seoul Press Conference, Korea, 1972 July (Box-folder 5: 25)
  - Departure statement, Taipei, Taiwan, 1972 July 5 (Box-folder 5: 26)
  - News briefing, Bray, 1972 July 11 (Box-folder 5: 27)
    Typescript transcript.
  - Address, China Trade Symposium, Graduate School of Business Administration, University of Southern California, Los Angeles, 1972 October 9 (Box-folder 5: 28)
  - "A New Platform to Build on," discussion with Henry L. Trewhitt, Newsweek, 1972 November 6 (Box-folder 5: 29)
  - Interview, post-election, as reported by Spencer Davis, Associated Press articles, 1972 November 8 (Box-folder 5: 30)
    Typescript. Includes typescript notes.
  - Interview, Kinji Kawamura, Chief, Asahi, Washington Bureau, Washington, D.C., 1972 December 29 (Box-folder 5: 31)
  - "U.S. Policy in East Asia," excerpts from address, Women's Forum on National Security, Washington, D.C., 1973 February 19 (Box-folder 5: 32)
  - "The Pacific Role in World Affairs," interview, Barrett McGurn, United States Information Service, 1973 March? (Box-folder 5: 33)
  - Statement, Subcommittee on Asian and Pacific Affairs, Committee on Foreign Affairs, United States House of Representatives, 1973 March 28 (Box-folder 5: 34)
  - "U.S. Policies in a Changing East Asia," luncheon address, National Press Club, Washington, D.C., 1973 June 14
    - Correspondence (Box-folder 6: 1)
    - Holograph notes (Box-folder 6: 2)
    - Typescript (Box-folder 6: 3)
  - Remarks, Marine Corps Ball, 1973 November 10 (Box-folder 6: 4)
  - "Long-Term U.S. Interests and Policies in North East Asia," remarks, Chiefs of Missions Conference, Tokyo, 1973 November 15-16
    - Background material (Box-folder 6: 5)
      Includes remarks by Henry Kissinger.
    - Holograph notes (Box-folder 6: 6)
  - Remarks, Labor Attaché Conference, New Delhi, India, 1973 December 10 (Box-folder 6: 7)
    Holograph.
  - Remarks, Junior AAA Independence Day Ball, 1974 July 4 (Box-folder 6: 8)
  - Remarks, Chiefs of Mission Conference, Honolulu, Hawaii, 1974 December 6-8
    - Correspondence (Box-folder 6: 9)
    - Typescript (Box-folder 6: 10)
  - Speech, U.S.-Australian relations, Asia Society, New York City, 1975 March 11 (Box-folder 6: 11)
  - "Australian-American Relations: Current and Prospective," speech, World Affairs Council of Northern California, San Francisco, 1975 March 13 (Box-folder 6: 12)
  - Address, National War College, Washington, D.C., 1976 May 12 (Box-folder 6: 13)
  - "Changing Perspectives in U.S. Diplomacy," remarks, Eighth Annual National Leadership Program, Poughkeepsie, New York, 1977 October 22 (Box-folder 6: 14)
  - Statement, Subcommittee on International Organizations, Committee on International Relations, United States House of Representatives, 1978 March 15 (Box-folder 6: 15)
    Typescript. Includes a supplemental statement, 1978 March 14.
  - "American Foreign Policy: Formulation and Implementation," remarks, Ninth Annual National Student Symposium, Washington, D.C., 1978 April 15 (Box-folder 6: 16)
  - "Diplomacy: The World's Second Oldest Profession," remarks, Armed Forces Staff College (as of October 30, 2000, name changed to Joint Forces Staff College), Norfolk, Virginia, 1978 June 1 (Box-folder 6: 17)
    See also: Folder 20 and Box 7, Folder 6.
  - "Global Peace or Global Conflict: A Diplomatic Perspective," address, U.S. Army Institute for Military Assistance, Fort Bragg, North Carolina, 1978 June 6 (Box-folder 6: 18)
  - "The Art of Diplomacy," remarks, Armed Forces Staff College (as of October 30, 2000, name changed to Joint Forces Staff College), Norfolk, Virginia, 1978 November 21 (Box-folder 6: 19)
  - "Diplomacy: The World's Second Oldest Profession," remarks, Century Club, Springfield, Massachusetts, 1978 December 4 (Box-folder 6: 20)
    See also: Folder 17 and Box 7, Folder 6.
  - "Resource Competition and the World Balance of Power," speech, Industrial College of Armed Forces, Fort Lesley J. McNair, Washington, D.C., circa 1979 (Box-folder 6: 21)
  - "The SALT II: Implications for U.S. National Security," remarks, National War College Alumni Association, Fort Lesley J. McNair, Washington, D.C., 1979 April 24 (Box-folder 6: 22)
  - "Expanding Dimensions of Diplomacy," address, Armed Forces Staff College (as of October 30, 2000, name changed to Joint Forces Staff College), Norfolk, Virginia, 1979 May 15 (Box-folder 6: 23)
  - "Pacific Overtures with Marshall Green," interview, Peter A. Poole, Foreign Service Journal, 1979 June (Box-folder 6: 24)
    Printed copy. Includes related material.
  - "The State of State," Guest Editorial, Foreign Service Journal, 1979 October (Box-folder 6: 25)
  - "Toward a New Index of Human Well-Being," Asian Wall Street Journal, 1980 June 20 (Box-folder 6: 26)
  - "The Far East and the Far West: Forever the Twin Shall Meet," remarks, University of New Haven, Connecticut, 1980 November 17 (Box-folder 7: 1)
  - "Asia 2000: Global Issues in Asian Perspective," lecture, Washington Center of the Asia Society, Washington, D.C., 1980 November 18 (Box-folder 7: 2)
  - Review of Green's paper on the concept of gap between rich and poor, Christian Science Monitor, 1981 January 20 and February 13 (Box-folder 7: 3)
  - Remarks, Subang airport, Malaysia, 1981 July (Box-folder 7: 4)
  - Remarks in response to articles in the Far Eastern Economic Review and other periodicals, Jakarta airport, Indonesia, 1981 July 23 (Box-folder 7: 5)
  - "Dimensions of Diplomacy: The World's Second Oldest Profession," remarks, Armed Forces Staff College (as of October 30, 2000, name changed to Joint Forces Staff College), Norfolk, Virginia, 1982? (Box-folder 7: 6)
    See also: Box 6, Folders 17 and 20.
  - "U.S. Foreign Policy in Asian and Pacific Perspective," opening address, Centennial Lecture series, Korea, 1982 (Box-folder 7: 7)
  - "The American Foreign Policy in the East Asia and the Pacific Area," lecture, commemoration of the centennial of Korea-American diplomatic relations, sponsored by Dong-A Ilbo and U.S. ICA, Seoul, Korea, 1982 March 5 (Box-folder 7: 8)
    Typescript and printed copy, The American Policy in Asia, 1982 March 6.
  - Interview, Kim Chae-hyok, Joong-ang Ilbo, 1982 March 8 (Box-folder 7: 9)
  - Statement, Subcommittee on Asian and Pacific Affairs and Subcommittee on Human Rights and International Organizations, Committee on Foreign Affairs, United States House of Representatives, 1982 August 10 (Box-folder 7: 10)
  - Commencement address, Class of 1983, Hartwick College, Oneonta, New York, 1983 May 28 (Box-folder 7: 11)
  - "The Unquantifiables of Progress," comments, Board Members, World Environment and Resources Program Committee, MacArthur Foundation, Chicago, 1984? (Box-folder 7: 12)
  - Review of Robert S. Litwak, Détente and the Nixon Doctrine: American Foreign Policy and the Pursuit of Stability, 1969-1976, Presidential Studies Quarterly, 1984 (Box-folder 7: 13)
  - Commencement address, Groton School, Massachusetts, 1984 June (Box-folder 7: 14)
  - "ASEAN – Background, Problems and Prospects," banquet address, sponsored by Defense Intelligence College and Center for Strategic and International Studies, Georgetown University, Washington, D.C., 1984 December 4 (Box-folder 7: 15)
  - "U.S. Policy toward Taiwan and the People's Republic of China," opening comments, Quadrilateral Seminar on Security in Northeast Asia, Japanese Center for Strategic Studies, Tokyo, 1985 April 2-4 (Box-folder 7: 16)